\documentclass[12pt,a4paper]
\usepackage[utf8]
\usepackage[brazil]
\usepackage
\begin ... \end
\title
\author
\date
\maketitle
\begin ... \end
This article determines the composition of functions $f \circ f\left( \right)$, where $f\left( x \right) = 3x - 1$.
The process involves replacing the value $f\left( x \right)$ within the function $f\left( x \right)$.
\section
In this article, we will calculate the composition of the function $f\left( x \right)$ of $f\left( x \right)$.
The composition of functions, defined by $f\circ f\left( x \right)$, is obtained by applying the function $f$ to the result of the function $f\left( x \right)$.
\section
Let the functions be $f\left( x \right) = 3x - 1$ and $g\left( x \right) = x^ + x - 1$.
Let's determine $f \circ f\left( x \right)$:
\begin ... \end
f \circ f\left( x \right)
&= f\left( f\left( x \right) \right) \\
&= f\left( 3x - 1 \right) \\
&= 3 \cdot \left( 3x - 1 \right) - 1 \\
&= 9x - 3 - 1 \\
&= 9x - 4 \\
&= \boxed
\section
We conclude that the composition of functions $f \circ f\left( x \right)$ is equal to $9x - 4$.